You slept in. It's like 8:50.
>> Hey, bud. Do you want to try going on
the potty?
>> All done with your milk.
>> Hey, do you want to go pee in the potty?
>> No.
>> Why?
>> You're silly. I love you.
Bare minimum makeup for this morning's
walk.
Excuse
me, Elmo.
A little chilly this morning, so we are
going to wear a sweatuit.
>> You want to wear this?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> Left leg, right leg. Oh, this is such a
cool outfit. You're so handsome.
Say, go potty room.
Sit. Now we're going to brush brush your
hair.
>> You're so handsome. Handsome boy.
Handsome. Handsome. My little monkey.
What's a monkey say?
>> We are meeting up with a couple of
friends to get breakfast and coffee. But
I'm also going to bring an applesauce
pouch. And then I'm also going to get
him a sandwich.
All right, buddy. We got to put your
shoes on. Our new bassinet for baby
number two arrived and the swing. And
I'm so excited to put them together. Hi.
Your dinosaur shoes. What's a dinosaur
say?
>> Can you say please?
This is a sign to look into car seat
safety for your child if you have an
infant, toddler, or whatever age child,
cuz it does be insane when people don't
properly buckle their children into
their car seats. The chest clip should
be at their armpits. This should not
move. Like, you should not be able to
move your stuff. Your kids should be
put. Okay? You shouldn't be able to
pinch here and you should not be able to
pinch here. Should be nice and snug.
>> What, buddy?
>> He wants his stick. This is actually one
of my back scratchers that broke.
>> You're welcome,
>> Mommy.
My van is making a very weird sound, so
I'm really hoping we make it to our
destination. My latte. I did a Teddygram
latte and then my friend did just a
regular latte. Two breakfast sandwiches,
one for Ken, one for me. And then a
tiger's blood drink.
>> And now lunch, nap time, and then we are
heading to a wedding. Have a good day,
guys.